<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CheTour</string>
    <string name="cooperative_name">CheTour</string>
    <string name="backArrow">back</string>
    <string name="home_screen1">Chernivtsi is a city in western Ukraine, located in the northern part of the historical region of Bukovina,
        near the Prut River. With a population of around 260,000, it is often called &quot;Little Vienna&quot;
        due to its Austro-Hungarian architectural heritage.</string>
    <string name="home_screen2">Chernivtsi is famous for its historic city center, cobblestone streets,
        and landmarks like the Chernivtsi National University, a UNESCO World Heritage Site. The university,
        housed in the former Residence of Bukovinian and Dalmatian Metropolitans, is an architectural
        masterpiece designed by Josef Hlávka.
The city is a cultural hub, known for its vibrant arts scene, annual literary festivals,
        and theaters. It is also home to various museums, including the Bukovinian Diaspora Museum and
        the Chernivtsi Museum of Local Lore. Its diverse heritage is reflected in its many churches, synagogues,
        and other religious buildings.</string>
    <string name="bacara">Bacara</string>
    <string name="bacara_description">Kav\'yarna on Teatralna Square 6 is a cozy coffee shop located in the heart of Chernivtsi,
        offering a picturesque view of the iconic Teatralna Square. Known for its high-quality 100% Arabica coffee,
        it provides a welcoming atmosphere for locals and visitors alike. It’s an ideal spot to enjoy a cup of coffee while
        exploring the cultural landmarks of the city.</string>
    <string name="bacara_address">Stepana Bandery St, 4</string>
    <string name="bacara_working_hours">Everyday 8AM-11PM</string>
    <string name="lviv_croissants">Lviv Croissants</string>
    <string name="lviv_croissants_description">Lviv Croissants on Teatralna Square in Chernivtsi is a popular café specializing in 
        freshly baked croissants with a variety of sweet and savory fillings. Located near the vibrant Teatralna Square,
        it offers a charming spot for a quick breakfast, snack, or coffee break while enjoying the city’s lively atmosphere.</string>
    <string name="lviv_croissants_address">Stepana Bandery St, 3</string>
    <string name="lviv_croissants_working_hours">Everyday 9AM-10PM</string>
    <string name="tvoya_mriya">Tvoya Mriya</string>
    <string name="tvoya_mriya_description">Tvoya Mriya Café, located at 45 Kobylyanska Street in Chernivtsi, offers a cozy and welcoming atmosphere. 
        Known for its all-day breakfasts, delicious coffee, and prosecco, it’s a perfect spot for a relaxed meal or a quick coffee break.
        The café is also pet-friendly, making it an ideal destination for animal lovers exploring the city.</string>
    <string name="tvoya_mriya_address"> Kobylyans\'koi St, 45</string>
    <string name="tvoya_mriya_working_hours">Weekdays 8AM-9PM</string>
    <string name="tvoya_mriya_working_hours_additional">Weekend 9AM-10PM</string>
    <string name="room_room">Room Room</string>
    <string name="room_room_description">Room Room Café, located at 5 Nezalezhnosti Ave, Chernivtsi, offers a cozy atmosphere with a menu
        featuring Pan-Asian cuisine, including dishes like bao with chicken, rice noodles with pork unagi, and various salads.
        They also serve breakfast items, desserts, and a selection of beverages such as coffee, fresh juices, and teas.
        The café operates daily from 9:00 AM to 10:00 PM.</string>
    <string name="room_room_address">Nezalezhnosti Ave, 111</string>
    <string name="room_room_working_hours">Everyday 9AM-10PM</string>
    <string name="shosho">Shosho</string>
    <string name="shosho_description">Shosho is a cozy restaurant in Chernivtsi known for its vibrant atmosphere and modern design. 
        It offers a fusion of European and Ukrainian cuisine, featuring fresh ingredients and creative presentation. 
        A great spot for casual dining or a special occasion!</string>
    <string name="shosho_address">Khudyakova St, 1</string>
    <string name="shosho_working_hours_">Wed-Mon 9AM-10PM</string>
    <string name="shosho_working_hours_additional">Tue 10AM-10PM</string>
    <string name="la_pasta">La pasta</string>
    <string name="la_pasta_description">La Pasta is a charming Italian restaurant in Chernivtsi, 
        celebrated for its authentic flavors and warm ambiance. Specializing in handmade pasta and wood-fired pizzas, 
        it provides a true taste of Italy with a menu that also includes delicious desserts and fine wines. 
        Perfect for a cozy meal or a romantic evening!</string>
    <string name="la_pasta_address">Kobylyans\'koi St, 20</string>
    <string name="la_pasta_working_hours">Everyday 9AM-11PM</string>
    <string name="kasha_maslom">Kasha Maslom</string>
    <string name="kasha_maslom_description">Kasha Maslom is a unique restaurant in Chernivtsi that combines traditional 
        Ukrainian hospitality with a modern twist. Its menu highlights hearty Ukrainian dishes like varenyky, borscht, 
        and creative takes on classic comfort foods. With its warm and inviting decor, it’s a perfect place to enjoy the 
        rich flavors of Ukrainian cuisine.</string>
    <string name="kasha_maslom_address">Geroyiv Maydanu St, 69</string>
    <string name="kasha_maslom_working_hours">Mon-Sat 10AM-7PM</string>
    <string name="kasha_maslom_working_hours_additional">Sun 10AM-5PM</string>
    <string name="fayno">Fayno</string>
    <string name="fayno_description">Fayno is a lively and stylish restaurant in Chernivtsi, offering a mix of European
        and Ukrainian cuisine. Known for its vibrant atmosphere and exceptional service,
        it’s a favorite spot for both casual meetups and celebrations. The diverse menu and trendy decor make
        Fayno a must-visit destination for food lovers.</string>
    <string name="fayno_location">Holovna St, 48</string>
    <string name="fayno_working_hours">Everyday 10:30AM-10PM</string>
    <string name="pronto_pizza">Pronto Pizza &amp; Sushi</string>
    <string name="pronto_pizza_description">Pronto Pizza &amp; Sushi is a popular spot in Chernivtsi,
        offering a delightful combination of Italian and Japanese cuisines. Known for its delicious pizzas,
        fresh sushi rolls, and vibrant flavors, it caters to a variety of tastes. With its cozy atmosphere and
        friendly service, Pronto Pizza &amp; Sushi is perfect for a casual meal with friends or family.</string>
    <string name="pronto_pizza_location">Nezalezhnosti Ave, 90</string>
    <string name="pronto_pizza_working_hours">Everyday 9AM-10PM</string>
    <string name="vyshyvanka_day_square">Vyshyvanka Day Square</string>
    <string name="vyshyvanka_day_square_description">The Vyshyvanka Day Square in Chernivtsi is a unique interactive space
        dedicated to Ukrainian traditional culture. Located in the city center, it features paths paved with cobblestones,
        modern benches, and waste bins. A distinctive feature of the square is its lighting: lanterns adorned with embroidery
        patterns from various Ukrainian regions illuminate the area. Additionally, QR codes on the lanterns provide information
        about the cultural significance of these patterns. The square also includes a children\'s playground, green areas,
        and bicycle parking facilities.</string>
    <string name="vyshyvanka_day_square_location">Kafedral\'na St, 2</string>
    <string name="shevchenko_park">Shevchenko Park</string>
    <string name="shevchenko_park_description">The Taras Shevchenko Park in Chernivtsi is a historic local monument of
        garden and park art, established in 1830. Located at 1 Sadova Street, it is a popular spot for recreation and
        cultural activities. The park covers an area of 16.9 hectares and features a lake, summer theater, amusement rides,
        and numerous green spaces. In 1990, the park was named after Taras Shevchenko.</string>
    <string name="shevchenko_park_location">Sadova St, 1А</string>
    <string name="popivskyi_square">Popivskyi Square</string>
    <string name="popivskyi_square_description">Popivskyi Square in Chernivtsi is located opposite the main building of the 
        Yuriy Fedkovych Chernivtsi National University, on Kotsyubynsky Street, 2. This square is a popular place for students
        and locals to relax. Popivskyi Square is an important part of Chernivtsi\'s urban space, blending historical
heritage with modern landscaping elements, providing a comfortable environment for leisure and cultural events.</string>
    <string name="popiviskyi_square_location">Universytets\'ka St, 58</string>
    <string name="park_zhovtnevyy">Park Zhovtnevyy</string>
    <string name="park_zhovtnevyy_description">Park Zhovtnevyy is one of the largest and most popular recreational areas in Chernivtsi. 
        The park offers a peaceful escape with its lush greenery, walking paths, and serene atmosphere. It is a favorite spot for 
        families, joggers, and anyone looking to relax outdoors. The park features playgrounds, sports facilities, and areas for 
        picnics, making it ideal for people of all ages. Additionally, it often hosts cultural events and seasonal activities, 
        adding vibrancy to the city\'s community life.</string>
    <string name="park_zhovtnevyy_location">Pylypa Orlyka St, 4</string>
    <string name="turkish_square">Turkish square</string>
    <string name="turkish_square_description">Turkish Square is a charming and historically significant area in Chernivtsi,
        located near the city center. It is named after the
        city\'s historical connections with the Ottoman Empire.
        The square features a blend of modern design and historical elements, including an old Turkish
        well that serves as a centerpiece and a reminder of its past.
Turkish Square is a popular spot for locals and visitors to relax, enjoy open-air events, and take in the
        picturesque surroundings. Its proximity to Chernivtsi\'s architectural landmarks makes it an excellent stop
        for tourists exploring the city\'s rich history and culture.</string>
    <string name="turkish_square_location">Sahaidachnoho St, 45</string>
    <string name="kobylyanska_street">Kobylyanska Street</string>
    <string name="kobylyanska_street_description">Kobylyanska Street is one of the most famous and picturesque streets in
        Chernivtsi, often referred to as the city\'s main pedestrian avenue. Named after the renowned Ukrainian writer
        Olha Kobylyanska, the street is a cultural and historical gem, lined with beautiful buildings that showcase a 
        mix of architectural styles, including Baroque, Art Nouveau, and Classical influences.
The street is a vibrant hub filled with cafes, restaurants, boutiques, and souvenir shops, making it a favorite 
        destination for both locals and tourists. Its cobblestone pavement and street lamps add to the charming, 
        old-world atmosphere. Throughout the year, Kobylyanska Street hosts cultural events, street performances, 
        and festivals, reflecting the city\'s lively and artistic spirit.</string>
    <string name="kobylyanska_street_location">Kobylyanska Street</string>
    <string name="chnu">Chernivtsi National University</string>
    <string name="chnu_description">Chernivtsi National University, officially known as Yuriy Fedkovych Chernivtsi National
        University, is one of the most iconic landmarks in Chernivtsi and a UNESCO World Heritage Site. Established in
        1875 during the Austro-Hungarian Empire, the university is renowned for its stunning architecture, particularly
        the main building, which was originally the Residence of Bukovinian and Dalmatian Metropolitans.
Designed by Czech architect Josef Hlávka, the complex features a blend of Byzantine, Romanesque, and Gothic styles,
        with intricate details, colorful roof tiles, and spacious courtyards. The university grounds include a beautiful
        park and gardens, offering a serene atmosphere for students and visitors alike.</string>
    <string name="chnu_location">Kotsyubyns\'koho St, 2</string>
    <string name="filarmonii">Filarmonii Square</string>
    <string name="filarmonii_description">Philharmonic Square is a historic and cultural landmark in Chernivtsi, 
        located in the heart of the city. This picturesque square is named after the Chernivtsi Regional Philharmonic 
        Society, housed in a beautiful historic building that has been a hub for musical and cultural events since the 
        19th century.
Surrounded by charming architecture reflecting the Austro-Hungarian period, the square features a welcoming atmosphere 
        with cobblestone paving, benches, and greenery.</string>
    <string name="filarmonii_location">Filarmonii Square</string>
    <string name="teatrlana_square">Teatral\'na Square</string>
    <string name="teatralna_description">Teatralna Square is one of the most iconic and culturally rich locations in
        Chernivtsi. Known as the heart of the city\'s theatrical and artistic life, the square is
        home to the Chernivtsi Regional Music and Drama Theater named after Olha Kobylyanska, a
        stunning architectural masterpiece built in the early 20th century in the Neo-Baroque style.
The square is surrounded by beautifully preserved buildings showcasing a mix of architectural styles
        from the Austro-Hungarian period. Its landscaped greenery, fountains, and open spaces make it a favorite
        gathering place for locals and visitors. Teatralna Square often hosts performances, cultural events, and festivals, reflecting the city\'s vibrant artistic tradition.
Whether you\'re enjoying a theatrical performance or simply soaking in the historic ambiance, Teatralna
        Square is a must-visit destination that embodies the cultural charm of Chernivtsi.</string>
    <string name="teatralna_location">Teatral\'na Square, 2</string>
</resources>